Hello everyone, we are NARUKARU b and today's project is
Today's project is "goo".
We're here to find out who knows the most about Mirai Suganami.
How are you doing?
I'm a member of the off-shoulder team, so I'm confident that I'll be able to do well.
I'm sure you're right... the answer's going to be a little weird...
I'm sure the answer will be "boo-boo".
The first question is this: What's the funniest thing that's happened to you recently?
I guess this is about as recent as it gets.
Really 3 days ago... 2 days ago...
That's a pretty good clue, isn't it?
This question is the hardest.
That's an easy one.
Was there someone else there?
Right now?
Someone?
I don't think so.
Good luck with that.
That was funny.
I heard you.
Wow.
I can't wait to buy it.
He's starting to play.
Okay, so...
Here's how we buy.
There you go!
Sayu, are you okay?
I thought it was soba, but it was udon.
What? That's totally different!
I bought two of my VCs by mistake.
Both buttons on the sleeve of one piece came off.
Just now. Just now.
Just now. - Just now.
Just now. Both buttons came off.
What happened?
I have my doubts.
It wasn't a day ago, so it's definitely not the same thing.
I'm sure. I'm sure.
Okay, so...
Here's how to buy.
I was going up the escalator.
I went down the escanator.
I've gone about two steps.
He did it in a funny way.
Funny, but...
Hazure
I'm not going to do it.
Your heart's not in it.
I'd like it to be where the members are.
All you do is complain.
It's hard.
I can't guess, and all I can do is complain.
Next. Next.
Here's the second question.
We asked you to tell us what you like about off-the-shoulder knitwear.
What is the best thing about off-the-shoulder knit members?
Hint
Everyone
The good thing about everyone
Put it all together.
Put it all together
I've got one. I've got one. I've got one.
Put it all together, right?
No, it's just the way it is.
I could write.
I could do it, too.
I'm sure it's right.
I got it.
Here are our answers!
There you go!
I like the forest.
Cute place
It's funny.
You know what I mean.
I get it.
It's funny.
You thought Mire-chan would say something like this.You thought Mire-chan would say this.
So here is the correct answer!
Eh, what's more...
Good point.
Everyone's talking.
What do you think?
It's good.
Everyone is talking.
I like the forest of equals.
Equal
Equals interesting
I feel like they are all different
Yes, they are.
Half.
Who was it for?
Half to who?
How's that?
I don't know.
He's cute.
Don't get me started on the cute part.
0.5 points.
Yay!
Cute.
That's cute, and a good place to start with that premise.
So here's the third question
Three, two, one to Mirei Soranami's bruised face.
Oh, really?
Are you going to do it?
I mean, what would you do, Mirei?
Face.
Oh, I can do it.
The usual.
I'll do the usual.
Ready in three, two, one.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's it.
Whatever you're doing.
It's kind of basic.
Right.
It's the only way.
The correct answer is this.
This is it.
You got it right!
This one.
All the noise members can probably do this too.
Correct answer.
Question 4 is here.
Now the number should be represented by 575
What a difficult question!
It's 575 right now.
Now it's 585.
Wow!
I win!
So here is our answer
Well then, let's go!
Oh, I want to go then!
I'm so embarrassed and nervous about this project.
585.
I'm sure.
Yeah, I'm sure.
When I'm hungry.
What's that?
Something sweet.
Oh, that's a first.
I made a mistake.
I'm nervous about talking to YouTube alone.
Oh, yeah.
It's possible.
It's okay, right?
I don't know.
It's good. It's good.
Okay, so here's the answer.
I don't know.
I don't know if I can speak.
Oh, wow.
But you look like him.
What?What?
Oh, but do it.
How's it going?
I made a mistake.
First one.
How's it going?
You like it?
Oh, God.
No, no, no.
Oh.
Ooh.
Oh!
I was shooting another project with you, but not even then, huh?
I don't know if it's that kind of thing.
Okay, so how many questions are we going to have next?
uhm... Buber.
pur właści?
I can go there.
I've been to so many places, it's hard to say.
Here's our pint
Ta-da!
Amusement park! Night view date! Illuminations!
This is a little bad.
The reason is that I often go to amusement parks with Mirutan.
I wonder if I'd still go to amusement parks if we became boyfriends.
I see.
He likes screaming, doesn't he, Mirutan?
I heard Saya knows a lot about nightscapes.
A night view date is a classic.
Wait a minute. Maybe this way.
Night view illumination.
I thought you were thinking of the night view type.
Wait, wait, wait. Night view.
What's that? Nightscape illumination.
Nightscape and illumination are different.
Wait a minute.
Night view was night view.
Of course it was.
So here's what you're thinking.
Let's see, a theme park.
Yay!
This way!
That's great!
That's a bit of a kizuna eye palette.
Oh, my gosh!
That's great! Yes!
It's true, a lot of night view dates are illuminations.
Then both.
How about both?
What's your point, Mi-chan?
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
This is so hard!
Now, let's move on to the sixth question.
What do you like about Hitomi Suzuki?
Where is it?
That one.
Wait, is this right?
I'm not going to write "favorite part". I'm going to write it as an image.
Ah...
That's the hard part.
It's hard.
Then write two.
Okay, write two.
You can write two.
Okay, I'll write two.
Okay.
My favorite part?
I wrote two.
Well, where are they? Wait, wait, wait.
Uh, wait.
It's embarrassing to write about yourself.
You're right, I do write nice things about myself.
I don't know why I'm starting to feel this way.
Yes, I do.
You got it?Did you have them?
Yes, we have.
So here is our answer.
Ta-da!
Saya's lending us stuff.
She said she'll lend us stuff soon.
Wait a minute, something happened...
She'll call me when she's done cleaning.
Oh...
You two are cleaning.
When you're cleaning your room, you call me while you're doing it.
Yeah.
That's why.
That makes a strong impression.
I see.
What is it? What's this?
I like the way he plays with me right away.
Oh...
You want to see?
No.
You look good.
Thank you.
I don't know... but he's called Hiiichan.
She buys me everything and then blows me off.
Me too.
This one.
Two of these.
These two.
But I wrote this one, too, the first time.
But I thought maybe they wrote it down.
I wrote it, but I don't know.
I don't know.
Here's the correct answer.
What is it?
I love it!
Reaction
I love the part where he says
When he says something, his eyes
and they get big.
What did he say?
What? What? What?
It's a reaction, it's a reaction.
There's no one here.
There's nobody here.
Oh, my God.
Why? Why? Why?
No, it's more subtle than that.
Last, last, last.
Reaction and...
I'm often imitated...
Hiiichan often makes this face.
Yes, you're saying that.
Yes, yes, yes.
She often makes a face like this.
Mirei is a bit silly.
Yeah.
Like that.
Like this...
I know, I know, I know.
She says she likes it here.
You're always doing that.
Right?
That's true.
But it's hard to tell at first.
I knew it.
I always ask her out right away.
I see.
That's harsh.
Tough.
She said no.
Saya has 2.5 points so far.
Hii has 1 point
I have 2 points and I have 2 points.
Hii...
I can't win!It's not impossible for me to win.
You've already lost.
I don't know.
If I'm too aggressive, I might get a service point.
So here's the seventh and last question.
Oh, no!
The first three best things about our customers get a point for every one of them!
So...
It's not hard to guess 3
If you guess one, if you guess one
I want to hit one, that's for sure.
I can do it.
I think I can do it.
So you can get 3 points.
I can do it.
I don't know.
But I wrote it pretty close to my favorite part.
I wrote that.
I'm ashamed of what I said.
Embarrassing.
You're right. And you guessed three of them.
I can't come up with three good things about myself.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
If you guessed three, it's a big turnaround.
I know, right?
I'm serious.
I wonder...
But you saw how they've come all the way here, and they're going with a curveball.
"Change of pace"?
Like facial expressions.
That's why I think he'll come up with a curveball.
That's for sure.
Okay.
Then let's go with this.
Here are our answers.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
That's right.
Good at taking pictures
You've got your own thing going on
You have beautiful eyelashes
Oh!
You just told me I have beautiful eyelashes.
Eh?
You like them.
Oops.
There's an oops.
Tell me.
I didn't write it.
Okay, Hii-chan.
You're great at managing facial expressions.
And that you're good at taking pictures.
And that she recommends anime.
I have an image of you always talking about it.
I see.
I'm also very energetic
We like the same things that you take pictures of
Oh!
But we're alike?
Yes, we are.
Photo management
Yeah.
Yay.
Yay!
Guys.
Everybody.
You're having your picture taken.
Everyone.
Oh, my God.
Here's the correct answer.
Third place.
You're fast on your feet.
2nd place
Talks a lot
No. 1
The part where he goes "wow" when he smiles.
eh?
Oh, wow!
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Cheerful, energetic, energetic
I have energy.I'm fine.
What? Why?
Why?
I think you're on the edge of expression control.
The last one.
I'm not on the edge.
What?
Why not?
But your eyebrows.
You were talking about it at school when you broke your eyebrows.
Yeah, I was talking about it.
Well, that makes it true.
But I didn't.
But you didn't.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Genki is the only one that fits.
Talks a lot
is vigorous
E-genki
I don't know.
Ha-ha-ha!
Nice!
Wee duck!
You're the one!
Eh, then...
So I'd like to announce the results!
Third place, Suzuki!
Wow, sis!
Sorry, Miru-chan.
I'm calling you again, so clean up!
Okay!
Second place, Saya!
I'm so happy!
First place goes to me, Akira!
Wow! The result is reversed! Too bad!
I'm most satisfied with my favorite part.
You're right!
It's so similar!
It's so similar, it's like...
Like a front.
Tatemae?
Japanesque?
I don't know!
No, it's like a premise!
Premise?
Yes, yes, yes!
I'm the King of Suganami.
Yay!
Well, well, well, well...
I was a little bit close, but everyone was there.
I mean, I called you a scab or something...
You know, it was close!
That was close!
It was fun!
Everyone seemed to know a lot about Mirren!
Yes!
Yes! So, I was the King of Suganami!
Yay!
Bye bye!